Privacy Policy

IQOPTION respects your privacy and is committed to protecting and respecting your personaldata. This privacy policy aims to give you information on how we collect and process anypersonal data i.e. information about a Client (as defined below) who is a natural person on thebasis of which that Client can be identified (hereinafter the data) in accordance with theapplicable data protection legislation and best practice.

We strive to create the most secure infrastructure of any broker in the world. In this privacypolicy we would like to tell why you can trust us with your data and rest assured that your datais safe.

It is important that you read this privacy policy together with any other privacy policy we mayprovide on specific occasions when we are collecting or processing your data about you sothat you are fully aware of how and why we are using your data.

In this Privacy Policy, unless the context otherwise requires, expressions defined herein shallhave the meaning ascribed to them in the Terms \& Conditions.

Please note that this Privacy Policy is addressed to current and prospective Clients. If you arean employee, contractor or a third-party service provider, your personal information will beused in connection with your employment contract, your contractual relationship or inaccordance with our separate policies which are available by contacting us at the contactdetails listed in the section OUR CONTACT DETAILS below.

If you are participating in our affiliate program and/or introducing broker program, we willprocess the data provided under our agreement with you to exercise our rights and performour obligations under or in connection with the relevant agreement and the term Client in thisPrivacy Policy shall be read to include the term Affiliate and/or Introducing Broker (asapplicable).

1\. WHO WE ARE

IQOPTION is a global brand, which in your jurisdiction, is operated by DIGITAL INVESTLIMITED a company registered in the Seychelles with company registration numberC8426374-1 and having its registered address at Seychelles, Mahe, Victoria, Francis RachelStreet, Sound and Vision house, suite 2 (hereinafter “We” or “Company” or “IQOPTION”). Weare the controller and responsible for the data of the Client disclosed to us in order to registerfor a Trading Account, Demo Account and/or to make use of any other services offered by usthrough the website (hereinafter “Website”) (this term shall at all times include Website’sdesktop and mobile versions).

This Privacy Policy is issued on behalf of IQOPTION the company responsible for collectingand/or processing your data when you use the Trading Platform through the Website, eitherfor a Trading Account or a Demo Account (or their mobile/desktop versions) (hereinafter

the Service(s)). We respect your privacy and we are committed to protect your data, whichwe collect, use and/or have access to.

We take measures to implement advanced data protection policies and procedures and toupdate them from time to time for the purpose of safeguarding the Client's data and the Client’saccount. Your data is protected by the legal, administrative and technical measures that wetake to ensure the privacy, integrity and accessibility of data. To prevent security incidents withyour data, we use a mixed organizational and technical approach based on the results ofannual risk assessment.

We shall not divulge any private information of our Clients and former Clients unless the Clientapproves in writing such disclosure or unless such disclosure is required under applicable lawor is required in order to verify the Client's identity or it is required for us to perform ourcontractual obligations under any agreement concluded with the Client. The Clients'information is processed only by our employees and/or trusted third parties which providespecific services necessary for the provision of our services. All such information shall bestored on electronic and physical storage media according to applicable law.

2\. DATA USAGE

1\. We may collect, use, store and transfer different kinds of data about you which we havegrouped together as follows:

● Identity Data includes first name, last name, and patronymic (if available), date of birthgender, passport, ID, Driver’s number, and copy of photo.

● Contact Data includes billing address, email address and telephone numbers.

● Financial Data includes bank account, payment card details and tax identificationnumber (including but not limited to social security number, income tax identificationnumber, national insurance number).

● Transaction Data includes details about the transactions performed by you, detailsabout payments, withdrawals, exchanges, trading history, profit, balance, depositedand withdrawal amount methods, and any other details in relation to the services youhave made use of through our Website.

● Technical Data includes internet protocol (IP) address, your login data, browser typeand version, time zone setting and location, browser plug-in type and versions,operating system and platform, and other technologies on the devices you use toaccess the Website and use of cookies stored on your device.

● Profile Data includes your Client Account details, username and password,transactions made by you, your interests, preferences, feedback and/or informationreceived through your interaction with us within the course of providing our servicesand survey responses.

● Usage Data includes information about how you use the Website, products andservices, registration date, account category, trading cluster, number of complaints,number of requests filed and IP history.

● Marketing and Communication Data includes your preferences in receivingmarketing from us and your communication preferences.

● Special Categories of Data/ ‘Sensitive’ Data includes details about your religiousbelief, annual income, biometric data and/or criminal convictions and offenses.

● Conformity Data includes details about your education, employment status, tradingexperience, self-assessment test.

● Banking Data includes details of the number of payment wallets and/or information ofyour bank card, including information of the issuing bank, card number, cardholdername, card expiration date, payment system, card validation code (CVV2 / CVC2), andphotos of both sides of the bank card.

● Data in KYC (Know your customer) includes identity document information, includingcopies of recently dated Utility Bills, Identity Card, Passport, and/or Driver’s License.

● Economic Profile Data includes details on occupation, purpose of investment, annualincome, net wealth, expected annual amount of investment and sources of funds.

● Location Data includes details on your actual location when interacting with ourWebsite (for example, a set of parameters that determine regional settings of yourinterface, namely residency country, time zone, and the interface language)

● Audio Data includes full voice recordings of calls that you receive from us or make tous. (the above collectively referred to as Personal Data)

2\. Aggregated Data includes statistical or demographic data for any purpose. Such data canbe derived from your data but may not be considered personal data in law as it will not directlyor indirectly reveal your identity. An example of such Aggregated Data could be that weaggregate your Usage Data to calculate the percentage of users accessing a specific websitefeature and/or services/product preference.

Notwithstanding the above, if we combine Aggregate Data with data in a way that the endresult can in any way identify the data subject, we shall treat such combined data as datawhich will be treated as per the provisions herein contained.

Processing of your data is carried out by us following the principles of lawfulness, fairness,transparency, and always adhering to the intended purpose of data processing, the principleof data minimization, accuracy, limited data storage, data integrity, confidentiality andaccountability.

In general we collect and process the Personal Data, for any of the following reasons:

1. To perform our contract with you,2. To comply with our legal obligations including without limitation to applicable anti-money laundering and terrorist financing laws and regulations (hereby referred to asmoney-laundering acts), and/or3. To safeguard our legitimate interest

The Client acknowledges that all or part of the data concerning the Client's account and relatedtransactions will be stored by us and may be used by us in case of dispute between us andthe Client.

The Client is responsible for updating any data provided to us in case of any change. Althoughwe will strive to keep your data up to date and review and inspect any information provided byyou, we may not be able to always do so without your help. The Client acknowledges that wehold neither commitment nor responsibility to the Client due to any aforesaid review orinspection of information.

3\. HOW IS YOU PERSONAL DATA COLLECTED?

We use different methods to collect data from and about you including through:

Direct Interactions. You will provide to us your Identity, Contact and Financial Data onlinethrough the Website and/or by filling in online forms and/or by corresponding with us by emailsor otherwise. Data may be submitted to us by you when you wish to:

1. Register for a Trading Account;2. Register for a Demo Account;3. Subscribe to our publications and ongoing updates;4. Request marketing and promotions to be sent to you;5. Enter a competition, promotion or survey; and/or6. Give us feedback or contact us.

We require to collect the above data in order that we are able to (i) provide our servicesefficiently, (ii) to comply with our ongoing legal obligations, including, inter alia, to prevent fraudand money laundering acts.

If you fail to provide the data when requested we may not be able to perform the contract wehave or are trying to enter into with you (for example, to provide you with our services). In thiscase, we may have to cancel a service you have with us but we will notify you if this is thecase at the time. It is important that the data we hold about you is accurate and current. Pleasekeep us informed if your data changes during your relationship with us.

Automated Technologies or Interactions. When using our Services, your deviceautomatically transmits to us its technical characteristics. Locale (a set of parameters thatdetermine regional settings of your interface, namely, residence country, time zone and theinterface language) is used for the purpose of providing you with the best possible servicewithin our platform. Using the information about IP address, cookies files, information aboutbrowser and operating system used, the date and time of access to the site, and the requestedpages addresses allows us to provide you with the optimal operation on our web application,mobile and/or desktop versions of our application and monitor your behavior for the purposeof improving the efficiency and usability of our Services. We use web analytics tools to trackperformance of our website and marketing source of users by cookies in order to optimize ourmarketing costs and provide users with better experience. You may at any time request thatwe refrain from any such transmissions (to the degree this is possible and subject to any ofour legal obligations) by sending your request to the DPO using our details in the OURCONTACT DETAILS below using the registered email address you disclosed and registeredwith us through your Account. We will address your request within 30 business days.

About Cookies:

A cookie is a small amount of data that often includes a unique identifier that is sent to yourcomputer or device browser from a website's computer and is stored on your device's harddrive for tracking site usage. A website may send its own cookie to your browser if yourbrowser's preferences allow it, but, to protect your privacy, your browser only permits a websiteto access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other websites.Many websites do this whenever a user visits their website in order to track online traffic flows.When you visit our Website, our system automatically collects information about your visit,such as your Technical Data, including inter alia to, your browser type, your IP address andthe referring website.

Cookies stored may determine the path the Client took on our site and used to anonymouslyidentify repeat users of the website and what pages were most popular for Clients. However,we protect the Client’s privacy by not storing the Client’s names, personal details, emails, etc.

Using cookies is an industry standard and is currently used by most major websites. Storedcookies allow the Website to be more user-friendly and efficient for Clients by allowing us tolearn what information is more valued by Clients versus what isn’t. You can set your browsernot to save any cookies of this website and you may also delete cookies automatically ormanually. However, please note that by doing so you may not be able to use all the providedfunctions of our website in full.

Please see our Cookies Policy for further details.

4\. PURPOSE FOR WHICH WE WILL USE YOUR DATA AND ON WHAT LEGAL BASIS

1. We process the aforementioned data in compliance with the applicable legislation asamended from time to time in order to (i) be able to perform our contractual obligationstowards the Client and offer them the best possible service, (ii) provide our Servicesefficiently, (iii) comply with our legal obligations, including, inter alia, to prevent fraudand money laundering acts, and (iv) protect our legitimate interests and your vitalinterests.

2. We process all data based on the following legal basis:

1. For compliance with our legal obligations;

2. For the performance of our contractual obligations towards the Client;

3. For the purposes of safeguarding our legitimate interests and your interests andfundamental rights do not override those interests; and/or

4. On the basis of your consent.

3. Indicatively we set out below, a description of all the ways we plan to use your dataand which of the legal bases we rely on to do so. We have also identified what ourlegitimate interests are where appropriate. Note that we may process the data for morethan one lawful ground depending on the specific purpose for which we are using yourdata.

- PURPOSE ACTIVITY TYPE OF DATA

LAWFUL BASIS FOR PROCESSING

INCLUDING BASIS OF LEGITIMATE

INTEREST

a.

1\. To accept to register you as aClient2\. To notify you about changes to ourterms or privacy policy3. To communicate with you andprovide you with secureidentifications, authentication andsupport services4. To confirm you are at age ofmajority as recognized and declaredby the laws of your jurisdiction

1. Identity Data2. Profile Data3. Contact Data4. Data in KYC5. Financial Data6. EconomicProfile Data

1\. Necessary to perform our contractwith you2\. Necessary to comply with our legalobligations

b.

1\. To perform our Scoring Processing

under which a Client is scored on a

scale basis with regard to the level of

risk he is to IQOPTION

1. Banking Data2. EconomicProfile Data

1\. Necessary to perform our contractwith you2\. Necessary to comply with our legalobligations

c.1\. To confirm the information providedby You under (a) above in relation toyour location. 1\. Location Data

1\. Necessary to perform our contractwith you2\. Necessary to comply with our legalobligations

d.

1. To secure authentication,identification and support services viasocial networks protocols and use thelinks to your accounts in socialnetworks for these purposes. 1\. Technical Data

1\. Necessary to perform our contractwith you2\. Necessary to comply with our legalobligations

e.

1. To process and deliver yourtransactions and requests (Deposits;Trades; Withdrawals)2. Manage payments, fees andcharges;3\. To collect and recover money owedto us.

1. Banking Data2. TransactionData

1\. Necessary to perform our contractwith you2\. Necessary for our legitimate interest(recover charges owed to us, make awithdrawal in case of breach of ourcontract)

f.

1. To administer and protect ourbusiness and Website (includingtroubleshooting, data analysis,testing, system maintenance,support, reporting and hosting ofdata)

1. Identity Data2. Contact Data3\. Technical Data

1\. Performance of our contract with you2\. Necessary to comply with our legalobligations3. Necessary for our legitimateinterests (take reasonable steps toconfirm that you do not use any waysto manipulate our platform \& forrunning our business, provision ofadministration and IT services, networksecurity, to prevent fraud)

g.

1\. To deliver relevant Website contentand advertisements to you andmeasure or understand theeffectiveness of the advertising weserve to you2\. To provide you with an optimaloperation on our web application,mobile and/or desktop versions of ourapplication and monitor your behaviorfor the purpose of improving theefficiency and usability of ourservices.

1. Identity Data2. Contact Data3. Profile Data4. Usage DataTechnical Data5. Marketing andCommunicationData

1\. Necessary to perform our contractwith you2. Necessary for our legitimateinterests (to study how customers useour products/services, to develop them,to grow our business)

h.

1\. to study how customers use our

products/services, to develop them,

to grow our business and to inform

our marketing strategy;2\. statutory limitations1. TransactionData

1. Necessary for our legitimateinterests (including statutory limitationsprovisions by applicable laws)

i.

1\. To inform you about any of thefollowing:— new services and/or products wemay offer;— Any new development and/orfeatures of the currentproducts/services we offer

1. Identity Data2. Profile Data3. Contact Data4\. Technical Data5. Usage Data6. Transactions7. Marketing andCommunicationData

1\. Necessary to perform our contractwith you2. Necessary for our legitimateinterests (to study how customers useour products/services, to develop ourproducts/services and grow ourbusiness)

j.

1\. To send direct marketing of ourservices to you always within theboundaries of our legitimate interests.2\. To send to you newsletters, push-messages and calls to keep you intouch with our new feature and newdevelopment of the currentproducts/services we offer, news andevents and the efficient provision ofthe full scope of our services.Please note that we will never useyour data to communicate to youand/or promote any third partymarketing material.

1. Identity Data2. Profile Data3. Contact Data4\. Data that maybe provided byyou during youractivity at theWebsite.Marketing andCommunicationData

1\. Necessary to perform our contractwith you2. Necessary for our legitimateinterests (to provide effective andpersonalized customer services to youand to update you in relation to ourservices that are available to you.

k.

1\. To allow us to provide you with theoptimal operation on our Website,mobile and desktop versions of ourapplication and monitor your behaviorfor the purpose of improving theefficiency and usability of ourServices.2. To use analytics tools to trackperformance of the Website andmarketing source of our Clients inorder to optimize our marketing costsand provide you with betterexperience.

1. Location Data2\. Technical Data3. Usage Data4. Marketing andCommunicationData

1\. Necessary to perform our contractwith you2. Necessary for our legitimateinterests (to provide effective andpersonalized customer services to youand to update you in relation to ourservices that are available to you).

l.

1\. to allow us to monitor and train ouremployees for your benefit2\. to safeguard your or our interestsin case of a dispute Audio Data

1\. Necessary to perform our contractwith you2\. Necessary to comply with our legalobligations

3\. to take steps for fraud prevention

4\. to improve the services provided toyou

3. Necessary for our legitimateinterests

m.

1\. To confirm that your annual incomecorresponds with your employmentstatus2. To confirm that you have nocriminal history. Sensitive Data

1\. Necessary to comply with our legalobligations2. Necessary to protect your vitalinterests.

4\. If you are an existing Client of the Website where we have a legitimate interest incommunicating with you, or if you have given us your consent we will collect and process yourpersonal data to communicate with you in case of support and/or sending newsletters, push-messages and calls to keep you in touch with our new features, news and events and theefficient provision of the full scope of our services. We will also use your data to send youmarketing information regarding our services that we believe may be of interest to you viaemail or otherwise.

5\. Our Website is not intended for children and we do not knowingly collect data relating tochildren. As we do not allow users under the age of 18 to use our services, we need to obtainyour birth date in order to confirm the Clients’ age checks.

5\. OPTING OUT

If you do not want to receive any marketing newsletters or transmit your data to the third-parties for marketing purposes, you can configure your preferences. Such configuring can bedone when (i) opening an account or (ii) when receiving such advertising content or (iii) bylogging in and going to My Account \> Personal Details \> Notification Settings. You may alsosend us, at any time, an email to support@iqoption.com using the registered email addressyou disclosed and registered with us through your Account asking us to cease from sendingsuch advertising content or sending your data to the third-parties for marketing purposes. Theaforesaid mark removal and/or e-mail received by IQOPTION will oblige us to cease sendingadvertisement content to you within 7 (seven) business days.

6\. DISCLOSURE OF DATA

We may share your data with the parties for the purposes set out above.

We take all reasonable steps so that our third-party service providers do not use your personaldata for their own purposes and only permit them to process your data for specific purposesand in accordance with our instructions.

In general, your data is used by our processors.

In addition, a transfer of your data to another legal entity may occur as part of a transfer of ourbusiness or parts thereof in the form of a reorganization, sale of assets, consolidation, mergeror similar.

With regard to the transfer of data to recipients outside of our related and/or affiliated entities,we note that we strive to maintain discretion with respect to client related matters andassessments of which we acquire knowledge. We may disclose data that concerns you only

if (i) we are legally required to do so; (ii) if required when you expressly order us to process atransaction or any other service and (iii) it is required for the provision of our services underour contractual relationship and/or (iv) protection of our legitimate interests and applicablelegislation as amended from time to time.

External Third Parties. Your data is shared with third party organizations/entities includingbut not limited to:

A. Service Providers. We may share your data with our trusted third party service providers,who, on our behalf, operate, maintain, and/or support our IT systems and IT infrastructure, ourwebsites, manage our payment solutions, perform statistical analysis, marketing andadvertising purposes, sending newsletters, provide customer support and perform otherimportant services for us.

B. Other related and/or affiliate entities. We may also disclose your data to other IQOPTIONAffiliate companies in order for them to provide us with the relevant services.

C. State authorities. Your details that are provided and/or that will be provided by you duringyour activity on the Website may be disclosed by us to official authorities. We will make suchdisclosure only if required to be disclosed by us under the applicable law or court order and tothe minimum required extent.

D. Other disclosures. In addition to where you have consented to a disclosure of the data orwhere disclosure is necessary to achieve the purpose(s) for which, it was collected, data mayalso be disclosed in special situations, where we have reason to believe that doing so isnecessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against anyone damaging, injuring, orinterfering (intentionally or unintentionally) with our rights or property, users, or anyone elsewho could be harmed by such activities, or otherwise where necessary for the establishment,exercise or defense of legal claims.

Where reasonably possible, management shall ensure that third parties collecting, storing orprocessing personal information, on our behalf, have:

a. Signed agreements to protect personal information consistent with this Privacy Policy andinformation security practices or implemented measures as prescribed by applicable laws;

b. Signed non -disclosure agreements or confidentiality agreements which includes privacyclauses in the contract; and

c. Established procedures to meet the terms of their agreement with third parties to protectpersonal information.

Remedial action shall be taken in response to misuse or unauthorized disclosure of personalinformation by a third party collecting, storing or processing personal information on behalf ofIQOPTION.

If you want to obtain further information on any data transfers mentioned above pleasecontact us using the registered email address you disclosed and registered with usthrough your Account through the points of contact listed in the Section OUR CONTACTDETAILS below.

7\. DATA RETENTION

We store your data for as long as reasonably necessary to fulfill the purposes we collected itfor, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, tax, accounting or reportingrequirements. We may retain your personal data for a longer period in the event of a complaintor if we reasonably believe there is a prospect of litigation in respect to our relationship withyou.

To determine the appropriate retention period for your data, we consider the amount, natureand sensitivity of the data, the potential risk of harm from unauthorized use or disclosure ofyour data, the purposes for which we process your data and whether we can achieve thosepurposes through other means, and the applicable legal, tax, accounting and otherrequirements.

We shall keep your data (including call recordings) during our contractual relationship and fora minimum period of 7 (seven) years from the date of termination of the Service used by you.

In general, all other data is stored for a period of 30 (thirty) business days after the date oftermination of the provision of our Services unless there is any other legal reason to keep it.

At the expiration of the data retention period the data is erased by irreversible destruction andwe also inform all third parties, to whom the data was transferred, regarding such erasure andrequest implementation of similar actions on their part.

8\. YOUR RIGHTS AND HOW TO WITHDRAW CONSENTS AND UNSUBSCRIBE

We ask you to provide us with true, accurate and updated information on your identity and notmisrepresent yourself to be another individual or legal entity. Any changes in your identifyingdetails shall be notified to us immediately and in any case no later than the 7th day from thedate of such changes. If your data is incorrect or incomplete, please contact us at the contactdetails listed in the section OUR CONTACT DETAILS below in order to change your data.

Under certain circumstances, you have rights in accordance with applicable legislation andour policies as amended from time to time. Some of the rights are rather complex and includeexemptions, thus we strongly advise you to contact us (at the contact details listed in thesection OUR CONTACT DETAILS below). You can find a summary of your rights below in thissection.

A. The right to access. You have a right to obtain the confirmation as to whether or not yourdata is being processed by us. In addition, you have a right to obtain more detailed informationabout the data kept and the processing undertaken by us and under certain circumstancesthe right to receive a copy of this data. In order to access and view your data withoutdownloading it, please go to the 'Access my data' in your personal cabinet, by logging ontoyour Account, go to Personal Data and at the bottom of the page you can proceed with yourrequest by selection - Access my Data. In addition, you have a right to obtain more detailedinformation about the data kept and the processing undertaken by us and under certaincircumstances the right to receive a copy of this data.

B. The right to rectification. You have the right to have inaccurate data about you rectified,and, taking into account the purpose of the processing, to have incomplete data completed.

C. The right to erasure. This enables you to ask us to delete or remove personal data wherethere is no good reason for us continuing to process it. In order to Delete your Account and allof the personal data currently stored in our system you can do so, by logging into your Accountgo to – Personal Data section and then Account Settings and at the Bottom of the Pageyou can proceed with your request by selecting- Terminate Account – Delete My Accountand all of its data. Please note however that we may not always be able to comply with yourrequest of erasure for specific legal reasons which will be notified to you, if applicable, at thetime of your request. In case if you want to obtain complete erasure of your data (to apply the“right to be forgotten”), please note that we may not always be able to comply with your requestof erasure for specific legal reasons which will be notified to you, if applicable, at the time ofyour request.

D. The right to restriction of processing. You have the right to request the restriction ofprocessing of your personal data (a) if it is not accurate;(b) where processing may be unlawfulbut you do not want us to erase your data; (c) where you need us to hold the data even if weno longer require it; or (d) where you may have objected to our use of your data but we needto verify whether we have overriding legitimate grounds to use it.

E. The right to data portability. To the extent the legal basis for the processing is yourconsent, and such processing is carried out by automated means, you have the right to receiveyour data in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format. However, this rightdoes not apply where it would adversely affect the rights and freedoms of others and/or incase it may be technically impossible to do so.

F. The right to object. Subject to the legal basis on which the processing activity is based,you may object to processing of your personal data. Please note that in some cases, we mayhave compelling legitimate grounds to process your information which we need to comply with.

G. The right to withdraw consent. To the extent that the legal basis for the processing isyour consent, you have the right to withdraw from that consent at any time. This may apply tomarketing purposes and/or with regards to the transfer of your data to third parties. In caseyou withdraw from a consent given, then we will cease to process your data, unless and to theextent the continued processing is permitted or required according to the applicable dataregulation or other applicable laws and regulations. The withdrawal from your consent will inno event affect the lawfulness of processing based on consent before its withdrawal.

H. The right to complain to the data protection supervisory authority. We do our best toensure that we protect your data, keep you informed about how we process your data andcomply with the applicable data protection regulation. In case you are not satisfied with theprocessing and protection of your data or the information you have received from us, then weurge you to inform us in order for us to improve. Please also do not hesitate to contact us, ifyou want to make use of your rights.

If you want to exercise any of your rights mentioned above and/or obtain more informationregarding your rights and/or our policies and procedures please contact us through the pointsof contact listed in the Section OUR CONTACT DETAILS below. Please also provide us withrelevant information to take care of your request, including your full name and email addressso that we can identify you. We will respond to your request without undue delay.

We may need to request specific information from you to help us confirm your identity andensure your right to access your data (or to exercise any of your other rights). This is a securitymeasure to ensure that personal data is not disclosed to any person who has no right to

receive it. We may also contact you to ask you further information in relation to your requestto speed up our response.

We try to respond to all legitimate requests within one month. Occasionally it could take longerthan a month if your request is particularly complex or you have made a number of requests.In this case, we will notify you and keep you updated.

We may charge you a reasonable administrative fee for any unreasonable or excessiverequests we may receive, and for any additional copies of the data you may request.

9\. DATA SECURITY

We have put in place appropriate security measures to prevent your data from beingaccidentally lost, used or accessed in an unauthorized way, altered or disclosed. In addition,we limit access to your data to those employees, agents, contractors and other third partieswho have a business need to know. They will only process your data on our instructions andthey are subject to a duty of confidentiality.

We have put in place procedures to deal with any suspected data breach and will notify youof a breach where we are legally required to do so.

Your help is always valuable in ensuring that your data is kept safe. Upon registration to theWebsite (or its mobile version), the Client will be asked to choose a username and passwordto be used by the Client on each future login and for the performance of transactions and useof the Services. In order to protect the Client's privacy and operation with the Website sharingregistration details (including without limitation, username and password) by the Client withother persons or business entities is strictly prohibited. We shall not be held responsible forany damage or loss caused to the Client due to improper use (including prohibited andunprotected use) or storage of such username and password, including any such use madeby a third party, and whether or not known to or authorized by the Client.

Any use of the Website with the Client's username and password is Client's sole responsibility.We shall not be held responsible for any such use, including for validation that the Client isactually operating in his/her account.

You are obliged to forthwith notify us of any suspicion for unauthorized use of the ClientAccount. You may contact us at any time through the points of contact listed in the SectionOUR CONTACT DETAILS below.

Encryption of your data in transit. Encryption provides a high level of security and privacyfor your data. When you enter your data in our platform we use strong encryption technologies(such as Transport Layer Security) to protect your data during transmission from your devicesto our servers.

For providing more trust and security we use digital EV (Extended Validation) Certificatesissued by trusted Certificate Authorities. You can see the ‘Green Bar’ in the supported browserversions which confirms what all transmitted data is secure.

Protection of your data in our infrastructure. We make it a priority to develop services thatare secure "by default". The "default" security of our services means that all new services andfeatures are designed with strict security requirements in mind before we even begin

development. This is the key to guaranteed protection and privacy of all data that our serviceshandle and store, once the service or new feature is released.

To secure your data, we use the pseudonymisation which allows most of our services tooperate without using your actual data. Instead of that, our services use a system ID that can'tbe traced back to identify you.

We are always vigilant about the security of your data stored in our infrastructure. Because ofthat we locate all our equipment which is used for your data processing in secure data centers.Network access to this equipment is isolated from the Internet. We use network segmentationfor isolation of services which need different levels of security from each other. In addition, werestrict logical access to your data for our employees on a "need to know" basis. So, only thepersonnel that really require access to your data for the purpose of providing you with our bestservice, will have access to it.

Threats protection. We are highly knowledgeable about modern threats to data security andprivacy, and we are well prepared to combat them. All events that occur in our infrastructureare continuously monitored, analyzed and responded to, which allows us to ensure properprotection of your data, keeping it safe from threats, vulnerabilities, and the effects of malware.

In the event of a failure that affects the accessibility of your data, we have data backup andrecovery procedures in place that will help us restore your data in a short time. To guaranteequick recovery, we use high availability mode enabled for most critical databases which allowsus to minimize downtime.

Employee awareness of data security. Our employees may handle your data in order toprovide you with first-class service. To guarantee the security and confidentiality of your data,we monitor all employees’ actions with access to your data in our systems and grant accessstrictly on a "need to know" basis: only employees who need access will receive it. We holdregular training sessions to make sure that each employee understands the principles that wefollow to achieve robust data security and privacy.

If you choose not to give your personal information. In the context of our businessrelationship we may need to collect data by law, or under the terms of a contract we have withyou. Without this data, we are, in principle, not in a position to close or execute a contract withyou.

If you choose not to give us this data, it may delay or prevent us from meeting our obligations.It may also mean that we cannot perform services needed to run your accounts or policies.

To what extent we carry automated decision-making and profiling. In establishing andcarrying out a business relationship, we generally do not use automated decision-making. Ifwe use this procedure in individual cases, we will inform you of this separately. In some cases,we may proceed with profiling in order to evaluate certain personal aspects. We shall informyou accordingly in case we perform any profiling. In general, any data collection that is optionalwould be made clear at the point of collection.

10\. OUR CONTACT DETAILS

We have appointed a data protection officer (hereinafter DPO) who is responsible foroverseeing questions in relation to this Privacy Policy. If you have any questions about this

privacy policy, including requests relating to the data, please contact the DPO using the detailsset out below:

Address:

First Floor, First St. Vincent Bank Ltd Building, James Street, Kingstown, Saint Vincent andthe Grenadines

Email:

internationaldpo@iqoption.com

To enable us to process your request, please contact us using the registered email addressyou disclosed and registered with us through your Client Account. We may require that youprovide us with proof of your identity, such as by providing us with a copy of a valid form ofidentification. This is to ensure that we appropriately protect the personal data we hold fromunauthorized access requests and comply with our security obligations.

If you have any questions, or want more details about how we use your data, you may contactus at the above contact details and we will be happy to provide you with further details.

11\. LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES

We may provide links to third party websites in our Website. These linked websites are notunder our control, and we therefore cannot accept responsibility or liability for the conduct ofthird parties linked to our websites, including without limitation to the collection or disclosureof your data. Before disclosing your data on any other website, we encourage you to examinethe terms and conditions of using that website and its privacy policies.

12\. CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

1. This Privacy Policy was last updated 09 May 2022. We reserve the right, at our discretion,to add, modify or remove portions of this Privacy Policy in the future to ensure that theinformation herein provides relevant and adequate information about our collecting andprocessing of your data.

2. This privacy policy may be supplemented by other information received from us and otherterms and conditions applicable to the Website or which you have agreed to as part ofyour interaction with us.

3. In case of updates, we will post the revised Privacy Policy on our website. Changes willtake effect as soon as the revised version is made available on our website. Yourcomments and feedback are always welcome. You may contact us at any time throughthe points of contact listed in the Section OUR CONTACT DETAILS above.
